petapixel.com 2019-06-24

# Privacy Policy

At PetaPixel, we place a high value on your personal privacy, and recognize the important of protecting your personal information. In this “Privacy Policy”, we aim to balance our business interests in obtaining and using your personal information with your reasonable expectations of privacy. Since this Privacy Policy may be changed at any time, we encourage you to review it often to ensure that you agree with the most recent version.

### When does PetaPixel collect personal information?

Ways in which readers provide personal information to PetaPixel include (but are not limited to): (1) by sharing your email address when subscribing to our email newsletter, (2) by sharing personal information through contacting us directly through email, or (3) by sharing personal details when leaving a comment on a post.

### What information is gathered?

In addition to the details described above, log files and analytics trackers used by this website store details such as the visitor’s IP address, referring page and time of visit.

Cookies may be used to remember visitor preferences when interacting with the website.

### How is the information used?

The information is used to enhance the vistor’s experience when using the website to display personalised content and possibly advertising. Contact information is occasionally gathered for giveaways, and used to contact the winner at the conclusion of the contest.

E-mail addresses will not be sold, rented or leased to 3rd parties.

E-mail may be sent to inform you of news of our services or offers by us or our affiliates.

### Who else has access to my personal information?

Some advertisements appearing on PetaPixel’s website are delivered by our third-party ad serving partners. Information about your visit to this site, such as the number of times you have seen a particular ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you on this site. Furthermore, in the process of serving ads to you through this website, third party advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

We have also contracted with a number of advertising network partners to monitor certain pages of our website and RSS feeds for the purpose of reporting website and RSS traffic, statistics, advertisement “click-throughs,” and/or other activities on our website. Where authorized by us, these advertising network partners may use cookies, web beacons, and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our website visitors. No personally identifiable information is collected by or transferred to these network partners. For more information about how the information is collected and used, please see the following:

[Feedburner](https://www.feedburner.com/)‘s privacy policy at [http://www.feedburner.com/fb/a/privacy](https://www.feedburner.com/fb/a/privacy)  
[Google](https://www.google.com/)‘s privacy policy at [http://www.google.com/privacy.html](https://www.google.com/privacy.html)  
[TribalFusion](https://www.tribalfusion.com/)‘s privacy policy at [http://www.tribalfusion.com/TribalFusion/privacy.html](https://www.tribalfusion.com/TribalFusion/privacy.html)

Third parties and web sites that have links on our site may also collect or use information about you. The information practices of other companies or people that PetaPixel does not employ or manage are not covered by this Privacy Policy.

### How to opt-out

If you have subscribed to our content, you may unsubscribe by following the instructions which are included in e-mail that you receive.

You may be able to block cookies via your browser settings but this may prevent you from access to certain features of the website.

You may also opt-out of receiving cookies from third party advertising networks by visiting [this page](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) and [this page](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/).
